{
    "id": "f841539ef44c4b84b1e6890373014aac",
    "title": "Compound Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The doctor ....................................... his wife attended the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as well",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c90f0d6c372c49d191592e3ad79d2134"
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager .............................................. the secretary has signed the papers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "as well",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d47bcd355c2c45dd944f5e619b56a5b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The students began to talk ................................................... the teacher left the classroom.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "as soon as",
                "no sooner"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dcd55e39792b4230ac540167ced111d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She started laughing ............................................. she was insane.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "if",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7a230cb995e84fa8a53767d52934e086"
        },
        {
            "question": "He speaks ................................................ he is rich.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "as if",
                "as though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "af30c79ae9a644538337fbb6a428f0d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "They talked ................................................. they were scholars.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d762449ec4fa438a892742b9cdc671a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He will play .................................................. he is unwell.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "even if",
                "if",
                "even though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7601c09d89764232a4748a59b3b3047b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I cannot admit you ....................................................... you have a ticket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "even if",
                "even after",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b0be68f8f57640ea98e99f6990f726ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "They climbed up a tree ................................................. they would get a better view of the procession.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in order to",
                "in order that",
                "so as to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "27f8f3e964e844e697d2c8d21bf9660c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can borrow my car ............................................... you return it before midnight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "provided that",
                "providing that",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c55ccb49f354815a4d6d997462ac890"
        }
    ]
}